[
  { "id": 1, "question": "Dog", "options": ["நாய்", "பூனை", "மான்", "கடன்"], "answer": "நாய்" },
  { "id": 2, "question": "Cat", "options": ["நாய்", "பூனை", "மான்", "பறவை"], "answer": "பூனை" },
  { "id": 3, "question": "Tree", "options": ["மரம்", "மண்", "புல்", "பழம்"], "answer": "மரம்" },
  { "id": 4, "question": "Rain", "options": ["மழை", "சூரியன்", "நதி", "மலர்"], "answer": "மழை" },
  { "id": 5, "question": "Sun", "options": ["சந்திரன்", "சூரியன்", "நதி", "மலை"], "answer": "சூரியன்" },
  { "id": 6, "question": "Moon", "options": ["சந்திரன்", "சூரியன்", "நீலம்", "மழை"], "answer": "சந்திரன்" },
  { "id": 7, "question": "Water", "options": ["தண்ணீர்", "பால்", "புளி", "சாறு"], "answer": "தண்ணீர்" },
  { "id": 8, "question": "Fire", "options": ["தீ", "நீர்", "மண்", "கல்"], "answer": "தீ" },
  { "id": 9, "question": "Flower", "options": ["மலர்", "இலை", "மரம்", "காய்"], "answer": "மலர்" },
  { "id": 10, "question": "Bird", "options": ["நாய்", "பூனை", "பறவை", "மான்"], "answer": "பறவை" },
  { "id": 11, "question": "House", "options": ["வீடு", "படை", "மரம்", "கல்"], "answer": "வீடு" },
  { "id": 12, "question": "School", "options": ["பள்ளி", "கல்லூரி", "வீடு", "மடை"], "answer": "பள்ளி" },
  { "id": 13, "question": "Book", "options": ["புத்தகம்", "குறள்", "பத்திரிகை", "பேப்பர்"], "answer": "புத்தகம்" },
  { "id": 14, "question": "Chair", "options": ["கோபுரம்", "நாற்காலி", "மேசை", "தரைகள்"], "answer": "நாற்காலி" },
  { "id": 15, "question": "Table", "options": ["மேசை", "நாற்காலி", "வீடு", "பள்ளி"], "answer": "மேசை" },
  { "id": 16, "question": "Apple", "options": ["ஆப்பிள்", "மாம்பழம்", "வாழைப்பழம்", "முட்டை"], "answer": "ஆப்பிள்" },
  { "id": 17, "question": "Mango", "options": ["ஆப்பிள்", "மாம்பழம்", "வாழைப்பழம்", "பழம்"], "answer": "மாம்பழம்" },
  { "id": 18, "question": "Banana", "options": ["ஆப்பிள்", "மாம்பழம்", "வாழைப்பழம்", "பழம்"], "answer": "வாழைப்பழம்" },
  { "id": 19, "question": "Car", "options": ["கார்", "பஸ்", "வீல்", "போட்"], "answer": "கார்" },
  { "id": 20, "question": "Bus", "options": ["கார்", "பஸ்", "வீல்", "போட்"], "answer": "பஸ்" },
  { "id": 21, "question": "Tree", "options": ["மரம்", "பூ", "புல்", "மண்"], "answer": "மரம்" },
  { "id": 22, "question": "River", "options": ["நதி", "மலை", "காடு", "மண்"], "answer": "நதி" },
  { "id": 23, "question": "Mountain", "options": ["மலை", "காடு", "நதி", "தொட்டு"], "answer": "மலை" },
  { "id": 24, "question": "Star", "options": ["நட்சத்திரம்", "சூரியன்", "சந்திரன்", "வானம்"], "answer": "நட்சத்திரம்" },
  { "id": 25, "question": "Sky", "options": ["வானம்", "நிலா", "மலை", "நதி"], "answer": "வானம்" },
  { "id": 26, "question": "Earth", "options": ["பூமி", "வானம்", "நீர்", "மண்"], "answer": "பூமி" },
  { "id": 27, "question": "Food", "options": ["உணவு", "பழம்", "காய்கறி", "தண்ணீர்"], "answer": "உணவு" },
  { "id": 28, "question": "Waterfall", "options": ["நதிபாசி", "நதிநீர்", "அருவி", "குளம்"], "answer": "அருவி" },
  { "id": 29, "question": "Friend", "options": ["நண்பர்", "பேச்சாளர்", "சகோதரன்", "அம்மா"], "answer": "நண்பர்" },
  { "id": 30, "question": "Teacher", "options": ["ஆசிரியர்", "மாணவர்", "நண்பர்", "தந்தை"], "answer": "ஆசிரியர்" }
]
